Like the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open
No place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through
The tarot spread
The magic's coming through
Transmission, yeah
That means you
Ready for your sale tonight
Beast kitty gang come running
The whole chat screamin' B to come back one more time
Thunder at the window Nancy rodin' on the rain
Pull the magician manifestin' defendin' sack his name
She got top panel box throws again
And there we go
Officer Alex McQueen, your man
Smoke machine and cuffs are trolling
Dragged some off the-
The hate I caught him in the light
Do I wanted him to be?
Not who he is?
That's the night
And Tony's on the tribe, you know buddies
What are my KZ?
KZ, well, you're under, like, you know, some other false name.
So that one.
Or you're just some wrong chat.
I got some coffee left.
Did I finish my coffee?
I did.
I have nothing left.
I think KZ has more food than me.
It's okay.
So they call artists.
They call them starving artists.
I'm starving.
I have a box of Twinkies, I suppose, I can eat.
Isn't that cute?
I like that, Sharon.
I like that video.
I mean, it made, like, you know, I think it made me, like, a female on a few scenes.
It made Jamie a man.
Alexander may have been white in a few of the scenes.
I mean, and then I said, Alexandra McQueen.
I mean, it was a little bit,
or Alexander the Neon Priestess.
It's one of those,
I got a little confused with some spaces.
But I think it was cute.
I loved Meese and the drummer.
I made him pretty hot.
I'm gonna come here and say hi.
Oh, I know, you wanna say hi too?
How are you today? Are you in the video too, Lunar?
Even tricks in the video, but they made tricks in black cat. Hi
Thank you. I was really playing it again. Isn't it good?
There's so much to it you have to see and then it says like even like the screen I got like the what's that in the chat and stuff
Let's play it again
Let's watch I'll watch it with you on the screen. May I comment through it?
Let the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open, no place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through the tarot spread
The magic's coming through
On to the transmission, yeah
That means you
My base kitty gang come running
a chance scream and be to come back one more time.
Thunder at the window Nancy wrote in on the rain,
pull the magician manifest in defendants.
Okay, hi.
Hey, how are you doing?
Good to see you, how are you today?
Hello.
Hi, do you hear me okay?
Hold on.
Do you hear me okay?
I'm not sure.
Does everyone hear me?
I'm sorry.
I have no volume on this side.
Let me try to rejoin.
Okay, cause I hear you fine.
Yeah
Hi
Yeah, it was just something weird goes on with the iPhone and
Chrome I have on your stream using Edge instead of Chrome
But how are you doing? Yeah, I think we're just getting comfortable with nor
Yeah, she she thinks she's like a parrot and you're a pirate. Yeah, I mean, it's like yeah
I'm like, oh my gosh never seen a cat
She's most affectionate cat I've ever really come across but you know, it's wonderful
But yeah, she does get on the shoulder. Hey, babe. Did you see some of the video that video?
I just made that it was kind of like yeah, I like the graphics a lot. Thank you
Well, some of it was like, you know, the Google thing, but then it's like I went and the Google thing did like all like the like the scenes like the like the picture for the scene, but then it only made three videos for me and then it's like so I had to take the pictures and make the videos elsewhere, but it still came together pretty good.
I like how I mean it's like that one was really like I had like, you know, the archive kind of analyzed for like.
Kind of like the lore and like this like the certain characters and inside jokes and so so that those kind of came up
Like yeah, like the thing that used to happen in the chat is kind of surprising
It's like but they've got some of the people wrong and like you know some of the but they got some of it, right?
So, you know, it's like it's always surprising to see what comes of right because that's amazing even for some things
Look, it's amazing that we even have these tools when I really
Think about it. I'm on like a little bit of a rampage making self-glorification
songs right now I made a new one yesterday um play it i haven't seen it
because i i wanted to premiere it yeah it's on the uh alexandra mares channel
it's called times on alexandra's side interesting i have a i have kind of a song with a similar
Um, like a time I think time is on my side. I don't know if I got it the times on my side
Remember that song that was in a dental Washington. Yes, I think all the fallen
That movie. Oh, did you ever see that one? That was a good movie. Yeah
They hear lately the angels talking to them. Okay, so um or angels or demons or I guess it was supposed to be like a
Zazel or something in that movie, but okay got your channel up. Okay, so this is your new song
This is called time is on my side.
Okay, got it, yep, got it, okay.
Let's check it out, I can't wait to see this.
All right.
Okay, got it, got it, ready, okay, here we go.
Okay, my mask is really slow, okay, there we go, okay.
Okay, and pull it up, there we go.
Okay.
Here we go, okay.
Time is on my side, all is under made.
that asteroth or there's like some kind of hot is it white okay is that asteroth
I mean it's like or ash ash tar or ash tar I kind of look like like a
Pallidian kind of a fame have you heard that you know only time will tell time
will tell I think I've been experimenting with different
Video generators and the one that I used to make that it let you input a story line
So I input a storyline that I've written like I don't know maybe five or six months ago
And that one's better. The only thing I don't I'm still not happy
With the character generation for the most part with the completely automatic video generators
think I'm gonna go back to making them a bit more manually yeah you know do you
see it on the screen yeah yeah I was actually surprised that they generated a
male character to look like that but
I'm a little disappointed in Ninja travel. So I have to go back to the I have to switch up
I know I mean watching he seems like a little bit boring. No personality. I was watching last night
I was doing a recap or a commentary and I just
Didn't like the energy
I mean, yeah, he was in the chat.
I was hoping he would be like, he wasn't even like, you know,
like, I see like he was maybe stoned or something like, you know,
just like unable to come to the panel.
Spit some game or something like that. I would have loved to see that. No, he's just in the chat kind of like
I don't think he has much personality and sometimes it's like that maybe to somebody else. He does but it's a
That happens and whenever
Like a personality doesn't match up with a look to me
I don't want to continue to look at it. Yeah, but let me tell you something. Can you
Just tell me what you think about this, okay?
May 7th of this year, I took down and disabled that site rumoredpedo.com
You would think that people would be
Happy about that who were on it, right? Can you believe that that girl pebs?
Lied on that stream. It's a good thing. I recapped it actually because I wouldn't have known otherwise
She lied to Zaya and said, oh, that site is still up.
No, it's not.
Yeah.
So what do you think she wants?
You think she wants me to put it back up?
Cause I can do that in literally five minutes.
I mean, they're still talking about like,
I know the other day someone was saying,
oh, there are, some people are kind of like, you know,
I guess intimidated by you.
And I don't know why it's like, because it's like you,
you really like have like, you know,
I would say, oh, I was gonna say about your video that's like so Saturnian a lot because I don't know if you know Saturn which is our birth ruling birth
planet of Capricorn, right?
Cap, it's associated with time and so when you had all those like those rings and the circles and
And then talking about time, you know, you kind of like I'm is on the Capricorn side. Yeah, I do I do believe that and so yeah, but um
But they were still talking about you had a wiki or whatever.
And I was like, well, I think that she had that's been down over a year.
Yeah, I was like, I think that's been down over since over a year ago.
I mean, I should just bring everything back.
I mean, if they're going to talk about it and I'm going to be demonized,
which is another, you know, characteristic thing of being Capricorn, of course.
But still, I feel like these people, they are oblivious.
to well to time to change to anything you know they want to run around in a
specific group doing it they're running around saying oh nobody sees that I've
changed nobody acknowledges my change well do you think jerks it's because you
don't acknowledge others who are trying to give you a chance that was me giving
that group a chance taken that site down but maybe it doesn't need to be down
Maybe not because I want to know why that chick lied and she lied very easily.
I am actually afraid of people who lie that easily because when you lie that easily about something small
Only God knows what you're also lying about, you know
Yeah, so I I'm I'm gonna you know continue because that was like a six-hour stream
I only got through like one hour of it last night
But I'm gonna continue today, and I'm just gonna keep harping on it. Why do you lie?
Why are you lying? What else are you lying about?
Because I don't like that shit
Initially, I was very nice to that girl. The only reason she came after me like she did was because of that chick Amber
and because she's naturally a very jealous person.
That's the only reason I never did anything to her,
but if she wants me to do something, I'll do it.
I'm a little hyped today, but I don't like that.
I do not like when people lie,
especially when it can be so easily verified.
Yeah, I mean it was like I mean I was kind of impressed almost that they like you know
I have like an affiliate thing and they have like you know a meet-up and like and are able to go to New York and stuff and
And you know those people I think are picked but then it's like they miss out so many good opportunities of like you know
Having a streamer house. They set up appropriately, you know, like I didn't do anything on that trip man
Yeah sat around
complained
nothing that they basically scam their audience.
Right, cause I wouldn't be sitting in a room
like with everyone on their cell phone kind of thing.
It was boring.
I mean, you got three people on camera,
people looking at you,
talk about something interesting,
play a board game, do something.
Well, yeah, I mean it's because they are because they are interesting people
I mean it's like the kids like you know go out be talking to people
They're in New York go to like a drag club and he gets a lap dance from a drag queen or something
I don't know like do something
Fun or something. I mean, I buy it if I had stuff funds up around here
I'd be going like all the time, you know, but it's like, you know, it's really like kind of like not but like they're
On vacation like on their big trip and it's like what is it going to be six hours of life?
Well, what else is going to happen like well, they're introverts they're introverts and
Unfortunately, they're a group of criminals
Using the streaming as a mask for what they're doing that they shouldn't be doing
But they're not good enough at it when it comes to using as just just be a criminal if you want to be a criminal
Why bother trying to act like a streamer?
If you're so much of an introvert that like all you do is say, give me money, give me money, give me money, give me money, and then you don't, you know, reciprocate, you don't do anything, you know, you don't show, you know, show out.
Why be on camera? Then why?
Yeah, I know well, I mean and well, did you see this thing like Brandon Q tagged me in a post and he's like he's like this guy
We owls out here or something like that
Yeah, Skelly, I guess, who I've never I don't think talked to ever like I don't think I don't recall ever meeting him
Or maybe I have a little Norse kiss it or maybe I have but let me bring up the brand and said oh
He there he's using a picture of you making fun of you his mods are all here making fun of you and stuff
I mean, I did have that situation today and I'm this guy
chat, yeah, Boo Sam's chat where this guy, I like said,
oh, we're gonna go rate his chat because I was playing
about how my like chat got rated by sure.
Wait, what are they saying to you?
Well, they go over there it like if I go if I say oh go read this chat like cuz I like cuz I'm just kind of like
I just like
Like having fun like talking to them over there
But by saying Skelly is fucking with you. He's thinking he's Skelly
I'm bringing up this picture and he's like he's like oh look at this picture that has
Skelly's posting on you in his background and so I want you to see I don't know if it's meant to be me
Let me grab my other device because I want to see okay
Yeah, it's fine.
Is it on Scali's tab or is it on Brandon's tab?
I think a few down on Brandon's, yeah.
Let's take a look.
People are getting a little bit nasty this week.
Yeah, I might be able to bring it up.
Is this it? Let me see if it comes up.
All right, let me go over there.
I think it's coming up on my end.
All right, it's on its post tab.
Yeah, I'm posting it like furniture through yeah, cuz I reposted something that he and I probably shouldn't have reposted it
But I did something else that he posted but uh
All right, let's see
Okay, here it is
That's supposed to be you
I guess that's a branded thing. I mean, I don't know if it is or it's like, I mean, it kind of like resembles like the Sandman.
Uh, I mean, it's kind of pixelated. I can't really tell.
We're in bra in it. Like, I was like, where am I?
Is it?
I don't know.
I'm not certain that's you I mean maybe it's does it look ultra pixelated to you
because it does it's kind of big I mean it's like I don't know if he like made it
like much bigger or if it was like and it's like I'm gonna screen cap it and
shrink it cuz maybe I can um
I don't know.
I mean, it could be you. Maybe it's you. Well, what is this from? It's from the thumbnail on this. Yeah.
It's a thumbnail. What's he talking about you? Because if he wasn't.
Yeah, psyche's nightmares. You look at what we out here has been using us on his thumbnails.
But I mean, we out here, was we out here talking about you?
Is that's who it is? I think I don't know if he has been or something like that. Like I think
I heard. I don't think he has been.
I don't know. I just don't know him. And so it's like I don't like it would be like not a reason to I'm gonna see
Where else? I mean that could even be him
It says weirdest dude. He's ashamed of ginger. He larps as brown hair. Okay. I see I see the character again
And where it says she's crashing out over Skelly and quitting the internet again
I see the same character
And I also see the same character where it says, let's watch some of these deleted streams and do some gaming.
I don't think that's you, but I would like to know who it's supposed to be.
Yeah.
Yeah, I see it.
Okay, so where he took the screen cap.
It's from welcome back to why was this deleted? That was another one. I'm gonna see if the character is recurring again.
I don't think it's anybody really. I don't think it's you.
Do you want it to be you?
Um, no, I was just wondering I was like, is this true or is like, I was wondering because I have, I don't have time, like actually there's, there's a new feature on YouTube, there's an AI on YouTube.
Like if you go around, I don't know if you have to enable it or something, but you can like ask it in my mentioned, mentioned in this episode and it will go through and it will like look through the transcript and find if your name is.
Oh, I don't even want to, I don't want to say that rabbit hole.
maybe someone else or something else that he follows.
Have you ever seen Kate's post of me?
She makes me like that same dirty like character.
Like, or they put me like shirtless.
Like I'm saying, man,
they've been playing this thing where I'm all.
It's not a bra.
It's a tank top.
It's a cutoff tank top and it's a cutoff shorts.
What if I if I click on it, maybe I'll click it. Well, I don't think that it looks almost like a werewolf
I don't think that's you. Yeah
Well, I mean, I say I mean look at me see if I can ask you questions. I can ask I can say analyze
Who else is?
Analyze video and I can ask it. I think a question
Because why would why would a character of you be next to big trolley? That's what I don't know
But it does have like a look of me
Well, I agree. I mean, I'm looking at it, but I don't see anything about it that really makes me think
It's you
Like the only reason I can see why you might think it's you is because what the hairline and the hair color
kind of like, it looks like that, like dirty, like where I'm all dirty and like.
If you, if you look at it, here, let me take a screen cap of this one and see.
What does everyone think in this? Is anyone in the shot?
I don't think it's you. I think it's, to me, it looks more like that guy who, um,
they were saying died or something. I think Crack Rock Chris.
I don't think this looks like you. I don't think it's meant to be you okay. I
Don't maybe it is look if it is big boom. I
don't for a lot of reasons I I I
Think it's just kind of like a random character that was somehow generated. I
Mean trying to think who else he talks to that it could be
Because you don't even have a thick beard like that
I'll see if like only think that because of the forehead in the hairline. Yeah, I'll see if like he ever said my name
I see by just search for like if you ever did a show with my name in or something
I don't think he ever did like uh, I almost want to say it looks more like good times than you
Yeah, I don't see anything like you know that he's posted. Maybe it's good times. Yeah
I don't know who it is. That's that is a weird odd
Maybe it is. I don't know. I don't think it like I'm looking at it. I'm trying to think what
Like the context there's this one where
It's that character and then I see
like a golden retriever
Which it makes me think of Christine
But yeah, then it's a guy sitting next to the golden retriever and I'm like well, that's not Chris
I don't I think he's just using
some sort of image generator and it's not really
Do you know doing what it's supposed to do? Yeah, because there's a lot of odd stuff
I think that he comes up with a theme and says I want a lot of people in it and it's just
Generating and it's probably
remembering on that account
Characters that I already created
Meaning the AI that's what I think
Yeah, I'm trying to show. Oh, it says that I'm looking to see if that character is there anymore in his thumbnails
I'm gonna get the photo of it. Let me see capture his part of page
Okay, let me look at this at this one right here because that might tell me yeah, I don't think that's you
You could ask him you could put a comment on his video and be like is that me?
No, I think it's good times because look I'm looking at one of his other things where it's photos actual photos of the people
and the picture that he's been using of good times has the beard and the hairline like that.
that's good times okay that's like oh yeah he's in the overalls kind of thing
maybe that's well it's not overalls it's a it's a tank top that's ripped and old
okay
But I'm looking at his other
Earlier streams like going back like to two months just to see who he's been um, you know talking about or recapping
And good times is toward the front of most of the group
Compilations
That's kind of funny though, it's kind of fun. I never met the Al for you out guy. I was watching
Yeah, well, I told you about that. Yeah
Yeah, like if you've met probably more people in the community in person than anybody I mean we're having you I mean
It's crazy to me to think about I was thinking about that the other day
Yeah, like everybody I mean it's like well you haven't make
You have to make you cue or um or um blogger. Have you or no? I didn't meet blogger, but um
I'm not gonna tell you why I did kind of make it known in one of my streams, but I'm not gonna repeat it
I'm on the west side of the country right now. I'm not in California, but I'm on the west side. Oh
Cool. Yeah, let's say. Oh my gosh. It's not much of a change
So I could theoretically meet more streamers, but you know what I think I'm gonna do I think what I might do is just um a
few days while I'm
on the side of the country.
Maybe what I'll do is I'll just position myself
and hang out and see if anybody shows up.
Oh, that'd be fun.
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, well, I mean but like I heard Brandon's getting like an RV or something or yes
So I saw some kind of like RV or something that he's like he's they forget IP to like look at the he's like
Here's a cute mobile or something like that. I don't know. Did you ever see that? It was like no
I didn't I didn't know he was gonna do that. Yeah, I think he
Still has a posted up like it was like a big
Let me take a look I don't see it now. Let me see. Oh wait, Q45 or branding Q. Branding Q. Branding Q.
Where is it on his post? I thought it was on his like, but I don't see it.
Oh, well, he's going after Skelly. Look at that. Uh-oh. Interesting. I wonder why. What's this?
Okay, I don't see anything about RV. Yeah. Yeah, I think I saw it yesterday. I thought maybe it was on a different
Maybe I was dreaming. I'm not sure
You know, but uh, he might have taken it down or something like that. I mean, but he might it looks like he has plans for something
He said like I think it's an FIP to
To his dad or something and then it's like he said that he said to get ready for like new investment for the Q army
Bulldeck company will be grand to opening soon. It was that what you were looking at
Oh, maybe maybe I don't think that's real. I think he's just, you know
I said there's he said the clumsy is a male escort
Yeah, I think that there could be something to that, considering the way that clumsy acts.
That's the one I reposted and I was like, male escort by the way, and then he ran with
it and posted something else, but clumsy is very fake, and I do not like that.
Yeah, I don't like that either, but if I scan it, what, like, you think he'll come,
You can scan it, I'm not gonna scan it.
I'm not gonna scan it, but it's like the scan is cut off
on the side, so I don't know if I want to.
Okay, I think he just made that, you know.
Well, yeah, then he had like this like thing
of like trishelicious, it was like, oh, it was like.
Oh, that one looked real.
I thought that was funny.
He's good at the AI art.
I don't know if that was, I mean,
it's like, was that supposed to be real?
Let me see, let me see if I can get this to 6am.
I don't think it's real.
I think it's AI, but he's funny. He has a good sense of humor sometimes
Okay, he gets mad. He gets real angry, but yeah, he does. He does
Post some really funny stuff. I like his observations at times and I do enjoy his streams really
Yeah, he just gets angry and
Right now at this point. I do kind of look past it because I've been there, right. I know
So yeah, he's an Aquarius and often times they like feel the anger of the world and stuff like that, too
He's angry and I'm blaming for being angry. I mean, I'm angry right I get why he's angry
because
He doesn't really do anything
But people keep coming at him and I mean it's the same thing this chick pebs coming at me saying that a website's active
That's not been active forever
But Sam man did that same shit when he kept talking about the wikis when I pulled that and I the whole time
I was like do you want me to put them back up bitch? Is that what you want?
And I think that is what they want. So they can claim victim have something to talk about
At like something's wrong. You know, it's just dump. See that's why these people are losing their channels. That's exactly why
That that is why but yeah, so I understand Brandon's anger because I'm angry too
I might not be angry tomorrow, but I'm angry at the moment
Well the other night I did hear you on betas and like, you know, you came
That you're okay with what I said. Yeah, I feel like if you two want them at some point
You know be friends or friendly or civil or more or whatever. I have nothing else to say about it
I'm not gonna be in the way of it. I'm not gonna be like what no I'm not doing any of that because
You know it's just
Yeah, I and I also knew to yell at that girl crunchy. Yeah, you know
To inform her that her boyfriend is in part black. I had to do that, too
He was on the time yesterday, and I kept trying to ask him but then I'm like
He was saying forever
That one of his parents is Egyptian or Moroccan or something. So now like what is he changing his story?
Right, I mean it's like that's why I went inspired me to do all this like I took I took like my genealogy report
I have a much more detailed one. Yeah, it's very interesting
Yeah, thank you
It's like and then it's like it has like these like there's a few like really cool things like I'm 99% of like the percentile of that website
Or whatever their database
connected to this elite
Celtic woman's burial in like 500 BC and that's like
so it's like there is like so it's in like pagans and said um it said adruids and it said vikings
those are like three like three groups like you know like really well you look a little viking-ish
yeah i feel like i want to what are those hats called that have the horns on the song
For helmets. Yeah, I like what is that? I don't like you know, you know, say I was saying ten
I was always like what does Tommy James would like to invite you to to his exclusive VIP private panel going on?
I I really
Um as many know I don't mention him at this stage and I have nothing else to say and I want nothing to do with that shit
Okay, that's me. But if you want to go because I'm gonna decline. I'm gonna decline. But yeah, but you um, but
Don't know. I'm just like, you know, but I do like I mean, I'm sorry
I put you in the last video like Alexandra and then it kind of mixed you with Alexander and then it was like it made you white
Made you black. I mean, it's like you it's just so you're touching your moods from imagination
Well, it's just a little bit of vitiligo
It's a Michael Jackson thing
But yeah, I'm gonna play I'll play the video again, but yeah, I love you
Um, you know, it's I'm not gonna be going on
I didn't even know I was in the video. I'm in the video. Well, it's a neon priestess. The neon priestess. Oh, the neon priestess one
Okay, Alexandra, but then it goes. Yeah, do you want to watch it one time before like? Yeah. Yeah, here's this new
Here's a new video. I really love this is what I made today has a lot of inside jokes. It's like, so here we go
Here we go
Like the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open
No place to hide
And nobody falters
The drinks walk through
The tarot spread
The magic's coming through
Welcome to the transmission
Yeah, that means you
Got the biscuits hot and ready for your sale tonight
Beast kid, gang come running, got the band
Chat screaming B to come back one more time
Thunder at the window, Nancy rodin' on the rain
Pull the magician manifest and defend and psych his name
She got time, same one shirt, bitch, I don't even know
His panel box just froze again, connection lost
And there he goes
Officer Alex, my queen and your man kickin' down the door
Hey, smoke machine and cuffs are trolling
They threw the arrows through the hate I caught him in the light night
Of who I wanted him to be
Not who he is
That's the night
It's Kate again, Tony's on the tribe you knew buddy
It was like a party, it's fun, it's fun, I like it
I really, you know, even if the characters don't look like the actual people, you can
still see the qualities in them, you know, it's good
There's something a page or an alexander officer McQueen. They even got his like Timu his team his Timu security guard, you know
I was like, I was like if you can't type officer because sometimes they didn't want to you know
Make the videos that's like, you know, get a police MSFC say you say most security guard
McQueen and then uh, no, yeah, Alex McQueen doesn't like isn't coming over anymore. He's like he's afraid. I'm gonna ask him
McDonald's or something like that
No, I mean I say I did it and I haven't I was like even this is a joke
I didn't say it but then he's mad about other stuff and like and then you know
I don't know I'm ghost is around my ghost's hours are like, you know
Like it's like so late. I've you know, Jamie hasn't come back for a while
I mean, it's like a big disaster, but you know, I'm glad that I have like, you know good friends
They still like him, but it's like a lot of people jump ship and then it's like kind of it goes to show like who's
It rotates okay because I mean I've seen people who host panels go from
regular six viewers up to a regular hundred and sixty viewers back down back
up it just it depends on it depends on the time of year it depends on you know
what people have going on in their lives some people they work seasonally and
when they don't work they watch us
Yeah, there's new people going but there are new people coming in but I really did like when you aren't beat is because it's like I think you were like
You know that girl crunchy just seems like very misled or naive or something
Well, I really just wanted to talk to beta, but I was I was very
Intoxicated because when I was talking to you I went through a whole bottle of wine. I'll admit it
And then you went offline and then I just remember thinking I'm not done yet
And I saw she was live and I was like, you know what?
Fuck it.
Oh, we have a guest.
I would like you to still do that.
You said you were gonna do an AI of her show.
I would love you to like, you know,
put one of her episodes through the,
through the, you know, LM, if you could.
But look, look who's here.
Wow.
Yay!
How are you doing, Goddy?
How are you doing, Alexander?
It's like, what's going on?
Hi.
How have you been?
I've been pretty damn good.
Thanks.
What's going on?
I can't complain about life, really. Other people can, but I can't.
I've seen his channel and it's like, yeah, it looks like there's like the grim reaper with this like, you know, beautiful, you know,
women with pink hair and there's at least love songs, so I think Goddy might be on it.
I'm always in love.
Yeah, but maybe there's a particular, is that the lady in England?
Life is full of love.
Is that the lady in England?
That's the one that told you to fuck off, remember?
Yeah. Yeah, I didn't bother her. I just said I don't know. She was joking bro. She was joking
She kept saying God he is God and I was like then she she donated to you after that. So everything was good. She did
Yeah, thank you so much. Well, you had to tell the truth
Yeah, what are you guys up to? Well, she's gold. We're good. We're just hanging out. Do you see like, you know, there's Lenore saying hi
This is my new my new apartment. See how clean it is. Oh, this is nice. Yeah, finally. I've upgraded a little bit
I've seen this somewhere before though. I saw somebody else have a place just like this. Oh, it must be one of those, um, you know
Tracked housing, you know, they're just they're copying you. Yeah. Yeah
Brady Bunch has a similar house, I think I heard you I heard you say a lot of people aren't coming by anymore
Yeah, I mean it's like I don't know I'm on a backup channel for for right now and it's like I'm
Monetization of getting back back as imminent and stuff and so it will like you know pick up and I've just been you know
I know because some people don't like the other things I've been trying but I may experiment or like I like to experiment and show
Different things and it's like I do have people that do enjoy some of the stuff and so
But yeah, people are like you know just saying oh well
It's because it's a moral thing and like and like I'm like the worst moral
Yeah
So you're gonna you're gonna change it up every now and then you're gonna change up your format. That's all
People are gonna keep watching you and don't yeah that they won't it's just it goes in waves. It goes in cycles and
There's some people with some agendas right now, and they're trying to demonize certain people and
You know like honestly
Look, I know Brandon ain't perfect
But I'm really getting sick and tired of people saying stuff about him that they shouldn't be saying that is not applicable to him
Right because I know it's applicable. I know it's not. Yeah
It's the same PDFs about everybody is like
There's actual child like crimes and children and it's up like this and it's like when people are saying people are 20s
Our children now and you know, it's like I understand. Yes, you know, the brain doesn't develop to 25 years old or whatever
Yeah, so and it's like yeah, and it's kind of weird when there's like such a big age difference, but it's like
You know, I guess we agree to rules as a society and it's like we shouldn't be throwing these words around for people that are doing the actual legal thing
Well, I guarantee you a lot of these people throwing this PDF around have excused a lot of PDFs in their personal life
I bet you all right
So it's all about people that they don't like or they're trying to cast it on other people because they've gone through or whatever
You know, but they throw it around a lot these days. I
Agree. I agree and it's like it's kind of the weekends like the real the real world
serious serious circumstances and situations and stuff, but
That's the world we live in I guess
So as long as you don't let kids on your channel, you should be fine
I don't I don't and it's like, you know, and that's one of the rules
So it's always been pretty much 21 and over like I don't think people you always do you always do try to groom that BG and that
We're that Billy Blanks or whatever the fuck his name is the weirdo that cat. Oh, he didn't kill his cat
He did some shit. I don't know what he did some shit
Yeah, I mean I guess he fought his mom. I'm getting blamed for fighting his mom, but actually if you look at him now he
wishes hair he looks like a japanimation character from
That's what it you know it. That's what he looks like a japanimation character. He does. Yeah
Yeah, he like the japanese like like will like animate like what they think are like, you know Americans or whatever
and they look like kind of like
Americans like I think you ever seen the boondocks Alex like I have you seen that I mean that's such a great show
But I think it's animated in Japan, but it's like takes place in the inner city kind of and I know what that yeah
I know what it is. Yeah, I mean it's if you ever see the animation of it
You'll be like this is animated in Japan obviously, but it's like animated ends, but then I can written and written and like everything else in the
US I think
It's pretty funny though. Like some of the animation is great, but yeah, I don't know man
Benny reminds me of like kind of like
There was this mood there's this animation Japan animation show called like
something about the devil but the devil comes to earth and he like works at mcdonald's he like he gets a job at mcdonald's
That's like the whole the whole show is like that he comes to earth and like loses all
What Benny needs to do is get the hell out of wherever it is that he is living and make a good solid try
As a traditional actor because he has the look and that look is going to fade quick if he doesn't hurry up
Right, because as it is, I kind of, like, yeah, go ahead and draw to you.
I got him. I just say anything. Okay. Yeah. Well, he has an androgynous kind of thing that is like
It was like yeah, I mean it's like once you I don't know when I went to Greece
I noticed like the women are like once they turn 39 years old. They turn into like a little old lady
They just like very hairy
Point but it's like then they like they're like they lose two feet it just turned into like the old lady immediately
It's like oh my god. There's like there's like you're like how'd that happen?
Well, I mean, I don't know at a certain age in Greece, what is it about that like some of these it's the hairiness they get very hairy
You know, and that's just it. You don't want to see that. Well, yeah
It ends up on the lip and everything. It's not it's not cute
So let's see what the Eastern European women are like this Mediterranean. I don't I don't know
But it's like the women are gorgeous
But then it's like the moms and stuff and the grandmas are like these tiny little little ladies, you know
And it's like it's like there's such a kind of funny thing
I don't know, I think they probably may have a lot of kids by 39 though.
You gotta marry young.
Yeah, but they're very loving, oh my god, they're very like the mother I had there,
like cause we did a homestay, and the brother hated me, but the mother loved me, and they
had a little fish restaurant on the beach, and they gave me like huge, she was the best
cook, and they would be like stuff, stuff peppers.
Great food is the best the lamb and the fucking potatoes and all that. Yeah. Oh my god. It's so good
I love that the food and I was a vegetarian like when I went to Thailand
But in Thailand they have like most of the vegetarian food and everything's like a very spicy
It's like so spicy, but I love like pod Thai
Do you go to Thai food ever or it's like really like I love Thai food
Better I like Asian food
There's a lot of nuts East Asian all that stuff. I can't Thai Thai food for me
I can't do Indian food. I love I fucking love Indian food to death, but Thai food
I can't do yeah
Well, you know that the peanuts and stuff and like the pod ties like they have peanuts in it and stuff
Indian food is good. They're good. So good. No, you go. Yeah, it's like I love all but I love all like ethnic food
I really like I'm experimental like at my family. We go to Chinese and like
Japanese and my favorite sushi is the yukura. Do you guys like sushi?
I love sushi. I do. I like the
Tempura rolls. I like, you know, just the sushi without the rice, you know, just the fish
Yeah
I love wasabi. I feel like there's almost a wasabi shortage. I've had a hard time
finding wasabi lately. Yeah. I like the powder to where you add a little water
to it and it makes like a paste. I don't like it pre-made. Yeah, I'll show you a
picture of the Ikura. Like I don't know if you ever heard of Ikura. Have you heard of Ikura?
No, what's that? So that's like that's like what I would always get like
At a at a Japanese restaurant like a sushi restaurant. We used to go to George's. Yeah, I'll show here. We go
George's sushi restaurant. That's a great place. Great name
There's like oh, there's like a real Japanese like George was like a real Japanese sushi guy, right?
But whatever right and like he's from Japan
that you have to be like you know trained to make sushi and stuff like but most people aren't right
but um let me see if i get this picture so this is what it looks like this this is my favorite
sushi which i would always get from childhood uh it's called being a samurai and here it is here
we go oh oh looks like looks like dragon balls those are salmon eggs they're salmon salmon row
But it's on the rice and then them and eggs. Whoa, that is good. Is it is it salty salty?
First mouth they're like literally like there's these balls that kind of burst in your mouth and they're like really good
You like that, huh? Yeah
I love that. I love the feeling of balls bursting in my mouth Scotty
Too easy too fucking easy, right? Oh my god, but this I've been hitting on these guys like Harry Tadzikas and
And I mean this guy named a food stamps. Oh Harry, you know what? He was talking about you three days ago
He was saying this site guy. I really got a crush on this guy. I mean I heard this
I didn't say why say anything because I know you but he was really talking very flattering of you
He said he loves your hair
he says that the way your hair glistens in the light he fucking found that like really amazing
harry right the harry guy the guy who thinks he's like on the magical tree he's yeah yeah that's
the one he was saying he's like psych is really a fucking cool guy i wish i could get to know him
and fucking go over and sleep over his house and stuff yeah you were saying this wow yeah dude you
should really uh nurture that that's a good one he hasn't come to my show i need to see he needs to
come to the show in zalo you know it's like i see him on other shows like he's on he hangs out with
He's over there all the time.
Hell, yes.
I know.
Well, and I like the guy who's the food stamps guy.
I said he looks like Henry Rollins with a screech wig.
Yeah, I don't know that guy. Okay. Yeah, I don't know him too much. Okay. Well, I mean, he's another like, you know
He's like all these guys from New York. I think they're black initially
Or something like that like none of them are black that I've talked they all have like some Puerto Rican woman screaming in the background about some
I got that for a while people thought I was black for like a minute
Yeah. I thought you were at first. I really did. Yeah. It's my eyes, right? Yeah. Oh, come on. Yes. Yes, that's what it is.
Howdy has that Morgan Freeman kind of smoothness to his voice a little bit. Well, you have like a heaviness to your voice, which a lot of times black males do have.
And that's why I thought you were black for a long time. Yeah. Now we know the truth.
Well, I don't know.
Sexy Italian.
I just picture George Clooney now when I think of you.
Yeah, a little sexier.
I made the pictures of what I think was great.
The AI was great.
That came out really good.
But I haven't animated you yet. Hmm. You have something brewing though. Don't you? Yes, I do
Cooking it's coming. Don't worry. I love you stuff man. You got that professional shit going my shit is so amateur
It's like I put a link backstage. It's like a 130 second thing
Show her how good my stuff is compared to hers
You ready to have your socks blown. Oh, here we go. So I think I have it ready. Here we go. Wait, our socks are gonna blow off. We'll see
Oh, yeah, they're gonna go out the window
Okay, here we go. This is post from Gotti
Okay, what do you have so it's self grandizing. Yeah, this is totally self grandizing. I'm sorry if it's started
I mean here we go. There we go. No, it's fine. Are you ready? Okay. Yeah
Okay
Got it here you
who is this guy that's a that's a king troll that i fucking put in the ground a couple days ago
for the final time so final knockout what does that say gaudy mania yeah gaudy mania yeah
are you are you the person in the red that's me in the red yeah that was me okay okay okay okay
yeah yeah what's this i didn't do this what the hell is that
Okay, do you think that that's psyche? I don't think it is. I think that's supposed to be good times. Who did this?
This guy known as skelly we owl here
He used to have the outcast owls and he does coverage of you know, some of the things in the communities that I cover
But Brandon thought that this was psyche. I don't think it is I think I think it's good times because of the beer
Um, the the the facial hair I think that's who it is. I don't think it's
Sight doesn't drink beer though. That's the thing. I can see that. I can see that. Yeah, beer. That's why I don't think it's psyche
Okay, I think it's mistaken identity, but he's a little a little too dirty to be psyched. Yeah good times
Yeah, we'd have to see his nails though
Clean today, I like good Bravo good man
Mmm, we're having a piece of cheese. Mmm. You live good. You live fucking good. Thank you
All right guys, why I gotta get going. I got some I gotta do real quick
Take care. It's really good talking to you. Goddy. Good to see you. See you later. Have a good night. Bye
Take care
God, did you see the new theme song? No play it. Okay. Here you go. Take this out. You'll love it
Like the candle, hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open, no place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through the tarot spread
The magic's coming through
To the transmission, yeah
That means you
Ooh, I got spread
Who's this?
Edith
The whole chat screaming be to come back one more time
Thunder at the window Nancy rodin on the rain for the magician manifesting defendants like
We're a glory, same one shirt for a year and I don't even know
This panel box just froze again, connection lost
And there we go
Officer Alex McQueen, your man kicking down the door
Single rose, Nate wants more pipe
Smoke machine and coughs are trolling, drags them off the bomb redeemer
They threw the arrows through the hate, I caught them in the light night
I loved who I wanted him to be
Not who he is, that's the night
It's Kate again, Tony's on the tribune, new buddies
things though. One, I didn't see me mentioned at all. And two, two was I didn't see the
spirit of Michael Leguizamo. Okay, Michael Leguizamo and you in it. Okay. How about you?
Yeah. Well, I figured it was only people that donated to the channel that God mentioned.
So that's yeah, that's all right. That was the Donator video, but ghosts didn't even make
that one. Donator video. See that folks? See that if you donate, you could be in the video.
that's the way it should be well you got a couple of videos out of me too no no i did thank you i
appreciate anything you've done for me you're welcome you've been very good to the gaudi brand
i appreciate you i have the gaudi brand well gaudi you know what you get um you get in the mail
what i'm a dalian a psychic cult medallion i've been waiting for one of these
is that what you want i hear the chicks love it yeah well let me be this one you have one
You said it keeps closing. Oh, there you go. What is this? You as Dr. Who?
It's gonna be me. I'm gonna do like a cheesecake photo shoot for you. Oh, great. You mean like a like a calendar shoot
Yeah, I'm gonna have like I mean, but I won't have pants or that were the for them. No, no, no
Keep the pants and the shirt on. Yeah, that's even better. Okay. That's good. That's good that way
That could be fall that could be like October right there. Oh my pants are gonna fall. That's for sure
No, that would be probably July you want to do that in July when it's hotter. Yeah, okay. Yeah
You know who loved that. Sam and I will buy like 20 copies of that issue. That'll be a good one.
But do two versions.
Two versions. I guess before I go, I'm gonna do like a, I'll do a reading. If anyone wants a reading today, you can look in this chat for the
instructions, but let me see.
I'll take one card if you don't mind before I go.
For sure. I got you a card. Hold on a second.
Okay.
I'm gonna map out the rest of my evening right now.
Ooh, Goddy. Look what you got. Oh, what is it? You got two carbs and one
The spider once is rain
What spider rain? Yeah
So it's gonna be raining spiders. It might be look at the she has her tongue out
I don't know what she's eating right there, but if they are rain is eating spiders, you know, right?
Do you know a rain? That's not good. Oh
What's raining? Oh, it is okay. That is crazy. There are spiders. Yeah, nobody wants raining spiders
Kingdom of the spiders which William Shatner and they took over the whole town and they put webs all over the whole fucking town
Yeah, that's creepy, man. Okay. I'm sorry. You ruin my night. Thanks. I
Okay, I love you. Got you. You're the best, bro. Be good
If I die if I die tonight your fault, bye
Okay, anybody before I go let me just check
me to check
Okay, well, I hope you enjoyed the show and doing back later tonight. Otherwise, I'll probably be sleeping tonight. So we'll see you later
The good hour. I love you